

About me

I am a full stack software engineer focused on building simple and elegant solutions to complex problems. I approach challenges holistically to build cohesive and engaging user experiences. I strive to always challenge myself as well as my coworkers to help create an environment that encourages learning and growth, both personally and as a team.

Skills

- React

 Redux/Reselect, Hooks/Recoil
- * Erlang/Elixir/OTP
 Supervision Trees, Cowboy, Phoenix
- * Functional Programming TypeScript, Elm, Haskell

Languages

- **★** English

 Native proficiency
- **⊁** French

 Native proficiency
- **☆** German

 Limited working proficiency

Education

* DUT in Computer Science at Université Savoie Mont-Blanc

Experience

Getsurance

Frontend Developer

03.2020 - Present

- Work on the existing products and lead the development of Getsurance's latest product in **Elm**
- Set up automated **end to end tests** on Getsurance's main products using **WebdriverIO** and **TypeScript**
- Implement a static site generator with strict validation using Elm and JSDOM to fetch and render data from Contentful

Arweave

Software Engineer

02.2019 - 02.2020

- Build decentralized web applications in TypeScript and React built on top and showcasing the Arweave Blockchain
- Lead the design and development of the new iteration of ArQL to let applications query the Arweave Blockchain using GraphQL
- Help the team package the Arweave node software more conveniently by leveraging Erlang/OTP releases

Oixxit

Full Stack Developer

12.2017 - 01.2019

- * Implement a high-performance, concurrent, intermodal journey search engine in Elixir/OTP
- Work on the web client using React, Redux and RxJS while helping introduce TypeScript to the frontend codebase
- Work across front- and backend teams to implement new payment provider, helping each team to understand the other's concerns
- Help the frontend team setup automates tests for the streaming search results by using RxJS Marble Diagram Tests

Webmecanik

Backend Developer

04.2016 - 11.2017

- Contribute to the Mautic open-source marketing automation project written in **Symfony**
- * Set up automatic Mautic instance provisioning for agency clients
- Lead development of a dashboard interface for agencies to manage their Mautic instances in Laravel and Vue.js